JONATHAN HAN KANG

(253) 508-8729 • kangjon89@gmail.com • GitHub • LinkedIn

SUMMARY

I am a highly engaged and goal-oriented professional with 6 years of experience. I have proven abilities to achieve goals by proactively developing product knowledge, going beyond the basic requirements and available tools to achieve business objectives.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- LANGUAGES: Python, C#, JavaScript(ES5,ES6), HTML5, CSS3
- FRONT-END/LIBRARIES: Angular, jQuery, Ajax, Mongoose, Bootstrap, Material-UI
- FRAMEWORKS: Flask, Django, Node.JS, Express, Entity/.NET/ASP.NET
- DATABASES: MongoDB, MySQL
- **DEVELOPER TOOLS:** GitHub, VS Code, Workbench

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Key Projects:

- Chicken Dinner (Black Jack) | https://github.com/kangjon89/chicken-dinner 2020
- Classic card game of Black Jack where the platform is designed for users to interact against a dealer. Bet amount, beat the dealer and continue to increase your bank.
- Full-stack web development integrating Python Django framework, AJAX, Django, HTML, and CSS. It allows multiple users to register and play the game of BlackJack. Features using technology using login and password validations, Bcrypt password hashing, Session and various schema relationships.
- Wish Manager | https://github.com/kangjon89/wish manager

- 2020
- Wish Manager is where the user may wish for the item, and was architected using Python Django framework with MySQL, HTML, and CSS.
- RESTFUL API Allows multiple registered users to coordinate travel plans and join travel itineraries via SQLite connections and a user friendly web interface. Featuring login validations, Bcrypt password hashing, Session, and various schema relationships.
- Hobby Center | https://github.com/kangjon89/hobby lobby

- 2020
- Hobby Center was designed using C#, ASP.NET Core, Entity Framework, HTML, and CSS in which registered users may plan fun activities and join other user-created activities.
- Features integrated are login and password validations, Bcrypt password hashing, Session, and one-to-many and many-to-many schema relationships.
- Freelance 2020
- Website for Happy at the Bay with HTML, CSS, JavaScript (volunteer project).
- Designed a menu to be displayed onto TVs to have the atmosphere more contemporary with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap (volunteer project).

PREVIOUS PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

PRODUCT SPECIALIST, MAZDA USA
OFFICE MANAGER, HI-TECH DENTAL LABORATORY

2017 - 2019

2012 - 2016

EDUCATION

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER APPRENTICE | Coding Dojo

2019 - 2020

Developed dozens of web applications in Python, C#, and JavaScript using a multitude of frameworks such as Flask, Django, ASP.NET Core, Entity Framework, and Angular. Created user-friendly sites utilizing CRUD operations and RESTful routes together with API integration. Collaborated with colleagues to implement both front-end and back-end solutions to a wide array of unique challenges and wireframe specifications.

GREEN RIVER COLLEGE | ENVIRONMENTAL SCIENCE STUDIES

2014 - 2015

PACIFIC UNION COLLEGE | ENVIRONMENTAL SCIENCE STUDIES

2008 - 2012